Takayasu Nasu

#112 1209 Jervis St Vancouver BC V6R2B6 / Tel: +1(604)376-2691 / E-mail: taka.beckham@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/TakayasuNasu / portfolio: https://www.i-nasu.com/ / App Store: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/queens-game/id1575671780

Profile

Senior Full-Stack Web Developer with more than 9 years of experience in Information Technology Industry. Experience In Requirements Definition, System Design, Development And Testing For Various Applications Like Client Server, Web Applications IOS Application, Android Application.

Skills

JavaScriptSwift	TypeScriptJava	ReactPHP	Vue.jsPython	Anguler.jsRuby	Node.jsHTML	JQueryCSS	Next.jsSCSS	
WordpressNginx	LaravelDocker	CakePhpGit/Github	RailsAWS	GraphqlCircleCl	 MySql 	• SQLite	• Apache	

Work Experience

Lead Front End Developer (Contract) - DPCode Inc. / Vancouver, Canada (May 2021 - August 2021)

- · Mentoring members, managing tasks, One-on-one meetings, and reviewing their sources. My team has 6 people including me.
- Front end requirements definition, spec design, implementation.

Full Stack Developer / Technical Director - Medix inc. / Tokyo, Japan (June 2017 - August 2020)

- Created SPA for centralized management which useful knowledge within the company that was stored in various locations. That SPA is made with Docker,
 Laravel, Graphql and Vue.is.
- As project leader, I selected technologies and supported members of the project team.
- Built a Staging environment and set a deployment system using Github webhook.
- · Worked closely with other developers and UI designers in an agile environment.

Senior Web Developer - Strawbag inc. / Tokyo, Japan (November 2014 - October 2016)

- Created a CI system that combined Bitbucket, Wercker, and Slack to support development when I built a job-search management site using the php Slim framework.
- Cooperated and built some web applications with the Chinese coworker. That's when I supported him by creating task management, specification
 explanations, sample code, and documentation.

Junior Web Developer - BTM inc. / Tokyo, Japan (April 2013 - October 2014)

- · Continued to release Smartphone game which over 100 php files, built with over 100 tables, used by over 10,000 people daily consistently.
- · Created Android application that uses polymorphism in its design which is made with Java and I manage team tasks.

Junior Web Developer - I-Freek / Fukuoka, Japan (June 2012 - March 2013)

- Modified an existing program made with Perl and deploy it on Linux while checking the Apache conf file with Vim.
- Supported Android app which uses GPS made with Java using Eclipse.
- Wrote clean and stable code and accompanying documentation.

Projects

Dpcode Academy - https://dpcode.academy (May 2021 - August 2021)

- Tech Stack: React/Next.js/Cognito/Api Gateway/DynamoDB/scss
- · People who want to study computer science, algorithms, and something like that can sign up for online classes from this site.
- · Students can know which lectures they have attended, and the instructor can control the content and duration of the lectures.

Queen's game (April 2021 ~ July 2021)

- App Store: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/queens-game/id1575671780
- Tech Stack: Swift/Realm/MVVM/RxSwift/Core Animations/Figma

S-Portal (Jun 2019 - August 2020)

- Tech Stack: Vue/SPA/Graphql/Laravel/Docker
- SPA for centralized management of knowledge related to site production, accessed daily by 80% of all employees

FeedLP (January 2018 - September 2019) - https://www.itstaffing.jp/lp/fd008/?mfeed=D210310647D

- Tech Stack: React/Go/AWS Fargate/Docker/MySql
- We made an API for the job information used in the feed ads and used React to display it dynamically. The UI is now ready to be updated without any work
 on the server-side.

Landing Page and Wordpress (Occasionally 4 to 5 site per year)

- Tech Stack: html/css(scss)/JQery/Vue.js/php
- Perfect coding using css grid and flex-box based on the design data (psd) to improve conversion rates.
- https://www.iprimo.jp/ | https://www.exchangeuse.com/ | https://www.nichiiweb.jp/kaji/

Original CMS (November 2014 - September 2016)

- Tech Stack: php/Laravel/Slim/Phalcon/Cakephp/Zend/Smarty/MySql/JQuery/JavaScript
- Creation of portal sites for group companies and renewal of architect office sites
- · https://www.pharmaproduct.co.jp/
- https://mynavi-job20s.jp/

Web browser Social game applications (January 2014 - October 2014)

- Tech Stack: php/Smarty/MySql/JavaScript/Jira
- · Continued to release Smartphone game which over 100 php files, built with over 100 tables, used by over 10,000 people daily consistently.

Education